<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Charan R</title>
    <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Charan R</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://charanravi-online.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://charanravi-online.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My 1st post</title>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/page/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charanravi-online.github.io/page/</guid>
      <description>Desc Text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Rules For Life</title>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/blogs/12-rules-for-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charanravi-online.github.io/blogs/12-rules-for-life/</guid>
      <description>12 rules for life &amp;ldquo;12 Rules for Life: An Antidote to Chaos&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Canadian clinical psychologist and professor, Jordan Peterson. The book provides a set of principles for navigating life&amp;rsquo;s challenges and achieving a sense of purpose and fulfillment.
The book is divided into twelve chapters, each of which contains a specific rule for life. These rules include &amp;ldquo;Stand up straight with your shoulders back,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Treat yourself like someone you are responsible for helping,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Tell the truth, or at least don&amp;rsquo;t lie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charanravi-online.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my About page! I&amp;rsquo;m Charan, a passionate Linux Enthusiast, open source contributor on GitHub, and a skilled Python programmer. I also have experience in Flutter, Selenium, and problem-solving and troubleshooting systems.
I have a deep understanding of Linux and its ecosystem, and I love exploring different distributions and tools. I believe in the power of open source software and enjoy contributing to projects on GitHub, where I collaborate with developers from all over the world to create innovative solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charanravi-online.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for visiting my professional portfolio. I would love to hear from you! Please feel free to get in touch with me using any of the following methods:
Email: charanravi.online@gmail.com
Phone: +91 8971297535
LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/r-charan/
Additionally, you can also shoot a mail about what some other projects that I can work on.
Thank you for your interest in my work. I look forward to connecting with you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charanravi-online.github.io/music/</guid>
      <description>When I&amp;rsquo;m not tweaking my repo, I compose music.
Achievements
 Featured on SoundCloud Radio hosted by Dylan Berry. Featured on The Rolling Strone Magazine and on their socials. Surpassed over 3,00,000 streams online. Peaked at #61 Position on House: Armenia charts on Apple Music.  Listen to my music on your favorite music streaming/download platfrom</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sats Converter</title>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/projects/satsconverter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charanravi-online.github.io/projects/satsconverter/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The satsconverter repository on GitHub (Originally created by bitkarrot) is built using Python and HTML, CSS, Javascript that converts Bitcoin amounts between satoshis and BTC units. The satoshi is the smallest unit of Bitcoin, representing one hundred millionth of a single Bitcoin (0.00000001 BTC).
I am one of the contributors of this project on Github.
This is currently a running website - https://rates.bitcoin.org.hk/
This is only one of the sites under The Bitcoin Association of Hong Kong</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terminal-Wiki</title>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/projects/terminalwiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charanravi-online.github.io/projects/terminalwiki/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The Terminal-Wiki project on GitHub is a command-line tool for accessing and searching Wikipedia articles directly from the terminal. The project allows users to retrieve summary information on a topic or query, as well as access full articles in a text-based format.
The project is written in Python and uses the Wikipedia API to retrieve and process data. It also utilizes the Pygments library to add syntax highlighting to the text output, making it easier to read and follow.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
