<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Charan R</title>
    <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Charan R</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://charanravi-online.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://charanravi-online.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My 1st post</title>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/page/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charanravi-online.github.io/page/</guid>
      <description>Desc Text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Rules For Life</title>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/blogs/12-rules-for-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charanravi-online.github.io/blogs/12-rules-for-life/</guid>
      <description>12 rules for life &amp;ldquo;12 Rules for Life: An Antidote to Chaos&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Canadian clinical psychologist and professor, Jordan Peterson. The book provides a set of principles for navigating life&amp;rsquo;s challenges and achieving a sense of purpose and fulfillment.
The book is divided into twelve chapters, each of which contains a specific rule for life. These rules include &amp;ldquo;Stand up straight with your shoulders back,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Treat yourself like someone you are responsible for helping,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Tell the truth, or at least don&amp;rsquo;t lie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charanravi-online.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my About page! I&amp;rsquo;m Charan, a passionate Linux Enthusiast, open source contributor on GitHub, and a skilled Python programmer. I also have experience in Flutter, Selenium, and problem-solving and troubleshooting systems.
I have a deep understanding of Linux and its ecosystem, and I love exploring different distributions and tools. I believe in the power of open source software and enjoy contributing to projects on GitHub, where I collaborate with developers from all over the world to create innovative solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ERpred: a web server for the prediction of subtype-specific estrogen receptor antagonists</title>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/projects/erpred/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charanravi-online.github.io/projects/erpred/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Estrogen receptors alpha and beta (ERα and ERβ) are responsible for breast cancer metastasis through their involvement of clinical outcomes. Estradiol and hormone replacement therapy targets both ERs, but this often leads to an increased risk of breast and endometrial cancers as well as thromboembolism. A major challenge is posed for the development of compounds possessing ER subtype specificity. Herein, we present a large-scale classification structure-activity relationship (CSAR) study of inhibitors from the ChEMBL database which consisted of an initial set of 11,618 compounds for ERα and 7,810 compounds for ERβ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charanravi-online.github.io/music/</guid>
      <description>When I&amp;rsquo;m not tweaking my repo, I compose music.
Achievements
 Featured on SoundCloud Radio hosted by Dylan Berry. Featured on The Rolling Strone Magazine and on their socials. Surpassed over 3,00,000 streams online. Peaked at #61 Position on House: Armenia charts on Apple Music.  Listen to my music on your favorite music streaming/download platfrom</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Probing the origins of human acetylcholinesterase inhibition via QSAR modeling and molecular docking</title>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/projects/acetylcholinesterase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charanravi-online.github.io/projects/acetylcholinesterase/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Alzheimer’s disease (AD) is a chronic neurodegenerative disease which leads to the gradual loss of neuronal cells. Several hypotheses for AD exists (e.g., cholinergic, amyloid, tau hypotheses, etc.). As per the cholinergic hypothesis, the deficiency of choline is responsible for AD; therefore, the inhibition of AChE is a lucrative therapeutic strategy for the treatment of AD. Acetylcholinesterase (AChE) is an enzyme that catalyzes the breakdown of the neurotransmitter acetylcholine that is essential for cognition and memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Towards reproducible computational drug discovery</title>
      <link>https://charanravi-online.github.io/projects/reproducible-computational-drug-discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charanravi-online.github.io/projects/reproducible-computational-drug-discovery/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The reproducibility of experiments has been a long standing impediment for further scientific progress. Computational methods have been instrumental in drug discovery efforts owing to its multifaceted utilization for data collection, pre-processing, analysis and inference. This article provides an in-depth coverage on the reproducibility of computational drug discovery. This review explores the following topics: (1) the current state-of-the-art on reproducible research, (2) research documentation (e.g. electronic laboratory notebook, Jupyter notebook, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
